(Sheldon:)Un-unravelable.
(Leonard(opening door):)Oh, hey, Penny. Wow, look at you,
all ready for your showcase.
(Leonard(opening door):)- You look great.
PENNY: Thanks.
(Penny:)I just wanted to come by and wish you
guys luck with your symposium.
LEONARD:
Oh.
- Well, thank you.
- You know, I gotta tell you.
(Penny:)A lot of friends would let their friend
go alone, but that's not you.
(Penny:)You are the kind of guy
who stands by a friend when...
(Penny:)When he has a symposium to go to.
(Leonard:)I don't know what to say.
- It's okay, Leonard.
- Oh, okay, all right, good.
- Oh, boy, group hug.
- Uh-uh.
- Uh-uh?
- Okay. So, what's up?
Well, Penny is on her way to perform in
a one-night showcase production of Rent...
(Sheldon:)...which we are unable to attend,
because we're going to a symposium...
(Leonard:)...on molecular positronium
given by Dr. Emil Farmanfarmian.